http://saltysaltzman.com/privacy-policy/

Welcome to http://saltysaltzman.com/ (the “Site”).We understand that privacy online is important to users of our Site, especially when conducting business. This statement governs our privacy policies with respect to those users of the Site (“Visitors”) who visit without transacting business and Visitors who register to transact business on the Site and make use of the various services offered by
Saltzman Home Improvement  (collectively, “Services”) (“Authorized Customers”).
“Personally
Identifiable Information”
refers to
any information that identifies or can be used to identify, contact, or locate
the person to whom such information pertains, including, but not limited to,
name, address, phone number, fax number, email address, financial profiles,
social security number, and credit card information. Personally Identifiable
Information does not include information that is collected anonymously (that
is, without identification of the individual user) or demographic information
not connected to an identified individual.
What
Personally Identifiable Information is collected?
We may
collect basic user profile information from all of our Visitors. We collect the
following additional information from our Authorized Customers: the names,
addresses, phone numbers and email addresses of Authorized Customers, the
nature and size of the business, and the nature and size of the advertising
inventory that the Authorized Customer intends to purchase or sell.
What
organizations are collecting the information?
In addition
to our direct collection of information, our third party service vendors (such
as credit card companies, clearinghouses and banks) who may provide such
services as credit, insurance, and escrow services may collect this information
from our Visitors and Authorized Customers. We do not control how these third
parties use such information, but we do ask them to disclose how they use
personal information provided to them from Visitors and Authorized Customers.
Some of these third parties may be intermediaries that act solely as links in
the distribution chain, and do not store, retain, or use the information given
to them.
How does the
Site use Personally Identifiable Information?
We use
Personally Identifiable Information to customize the Site, to make appropriate
service offerings, and to fulfill buying and selling requests on the Site. We
may email Visitors and Authorized Customers about research or purchase and
selling opportunities on the Site or information related to the subject matter
of the Site. We may also use Personally Identifiable Information to contact
Visitors and Authorized Customers in response to specific inquiries, or to
provide requested information.
With whom
may the information may be shared?
Personally
Identifiable Information about Authorized Customers may be shared with other
Authorized Customers who wish to evaluate potential transactions with other
Authorized Customers. We may share aggregated information about our Visitors,
including the demographics of our Visitors and Authorized Customers, with our
affiliated agencies and third party vendors. We also offer the opportunity to
“opt out” of receiving information or being contacted by us or by any agency
acting on our behalf.
How is
Personally Identifiable Information stored?
Personally Identifiable Information collected by
Saltzman Home Improvement
is securely stored and is not accessible to third parties or employees of
Saltzman Home Improvement  except for use as indicated above.
What choices
are available to Visitors regarding collection, use and distribution of the
information?
Visitors and
Authorized Customers may opt out of receiving unsolicited information from or
being contacted by us and/or our vendors and affiliated agencies by responding
to emails as instructed, or by contacting us.
Are Cookies
Used on the Site?
Cookies are
used for a variety of reasons. We use Cookies to obtain information about the
preferences of our Visitors and the services they select. We also use Cookies
for security purposes to protect our Authorized Customers. For example, if an
Authorized Customer is logged on and the site is unused for more than 10
minutes, we will automatically log the Authorized Customer off.
How does
Saltzman Home Improvement  use login information?
Saltzman Home Improvement  uses login information, including, but not limited to, IP addresses, ISPs, and browser types, to analyze trends, administer the Site, track a user’s movement and use, and gather broad demographic information.
What partners or service providers have access to Personally Identifiable Information from Visitors and/or Authorized Customers on the Site?
Saltzman Home Improvement
has entered into and will continue to enter into partnerships and other affiliations with a number of vendors. Such vendors may have access to certain Personally Identifiable Information on a need to know basis for evaluating Authorized Customers for service eligibility. Our privacy policy does not cover their collection or use of this information. Disclosure of Personally Identifiable Information to comply with law. We will disclose Personally Identifiable Information in order to comply with a court order or subpoena or a request from a law enforcement agency to release information. We will also disclose Personally Identifiable Information when reasonably necessary to protect the safety of our Visitors and Authorized Customers.
How does the
Site keep Personally Identifiable Information secure?
All of our
employees are familiar with our security policy and practices. The Personally
Identifiable Information of our Visitors and Authorized Customers is only
accessible to a limited number of qualified employees who are given a password
in order to gain access to the information. We audit our security systems and
processes on a regular basis. Sensitive information, such as credit card
numbers or social security numbers, is protected by encryption protocols, in
place to protect information sent over the Internet. While we take commercially
reasonable measures to maintain a secure site, electronic communications and
databases are subject to errors, tampering and break-ins, and we cannot
guarantee or warrant that such events will not take place and we will not be
liable to Visitors or Authorized Customers for any such occurrences.
How can
Visitors correct any inaccuracies in Personally Identifiable Information?
Visitors and Authorized Customers may contact us to update Personally Identifiable Information about them or to correct any inaccuracies by emailing us.
Can a
Visitor delete or deactivate Personally Identifiable Information collected by
the Site?
We provide
Visitors and Authorized Customers with a mechanism to delete/deactivate
Personally Identifiable Information from the Site’s database by contacting .
However, because of backups and records of deletions, it may be impossible to
delete a Visitor’s entry without retaining some residual information. An
individual who requests to have Personally Identifiable Information deactivated
will have this information functionally deleted, and we will not sell,
transfer, or use Personally Identifiable Information relating to that individual
in any way moving forward.
What happens
if the Privacy Policy Changes?
We will let
our Visitors and Authorized Customers know about changes to our privacy policy
by posting such changes on the Site. However, if we are changing our privacy
policy in a manner that might cause disclosure of Personally Identifiable
Information that a Visitor or Authorized Customer has previously requested not
be disclosed, we will contact such Visitor or Authorized Customer to allow such
Visitor or Authorized Customer to prevent such disclosure.
Links:
http://saltysaltzman.com/ contains links to other web sites. Please note that when you click on one of these links, you are moving to another web site. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of these linked sites as their privacy policies may differ from ours.
Recent Posts
32 tips to improve your house with little money
Decorate the home with trend prints
A Checklist for Home Cleaning Services
20 tips to improve your house for little money
Decorate a bedroom with matching walls and curtains
